In the description in the comments below,
there is a link.
You click that,
you upload your Instagram handle
and your website.
I critique it. I'm going through,
I'm going in dry.
No bloody research at all.
Ready Play Golf.
We begin with Ready Play Golf.
Play Ready Golf.
Okay, 36 posts. You are early, bro.
Now what's going to happen here
is straight away, six weeks, five
weeks, four weeks, three weeks. You
are not posting enough.
Straight away, I look at that. 36 posts.
To even have 119 followers is pretty good.
Okay, this hates.
You are the brand. Can't say this enough.
You, that guy there talking in the videos,
you're the brand. Not this.
No one is falling in love with this logo
or that as a concept.
Going to bring in one of my big hitters
from the mentorship.
Ryan Moak is the brand. Oh,
I'm not following him on my business page.
858 posts, 46,000 following.
People say to their friends,
"Oh, do you follow Ryan Moak online?" "No.
Who is he?" "Mate,
he's this golf expert." Every shot I
was hitting was flinging
off to the right.
I can even show you now how good Ryan is.
Just going to learn a lot today because I
told him to come teach me how to play
golf. And there's a fun fact for you,
I hate golf. Hate it.
You've got your-
Do swing them out to the right a little
bit.
Yeah.
Can we build on it?
We can build on it.
Because that way, I'm excited to see this.
Yeah.
This is like me watching people do jujitsu
for the first time.
The second he saw me do a swing, he said,
"This is going to the right."
It's okay. I think a toe ball into the
water could be first shot.
I had no idea what that meant.
Just by your move.
That means that way.
Yeah. Just by your movement.
I do swing them out to the right a little
bit.
Yeah.
Can we build on it?
We can build on it. Yeah.
So what would I need to do to-
So yeah, that was good.
There's no point showing you what he
taught me because I did none of it.
There you go. Perfect. More.
And then close up that thumb.
I have no idea where that's gone. Now,
someone could watch this video, excuse the
fact that the sound wasn't well-treated,
and they would go, "This guy knows what
he's on about." Someone would go, "Oh,
do you know what?
I feel like I need some professional
help." They'd go, "Oh, mate,
there's this guy
online, Ryan Moak,
you need to follow him."
And that's what is happening because
this guy is making so much money,
he doesn't know what to do with it.
And you can see here, there
is a bucket of video content that
is working very
well for him. Fantastic. Look at that.
1.7 million views.
Anyway, it's not about Ryan,
it's about you.
So you need to be the representative of
your brand.
The same way that all my profiles say
James Smith.
There is no business mentorship Instagram.
There is a James Smith business.
Personal brand, businesses.
Daniel Priestley, Dent Media.
Chris Williamson, Modern Wisdom.
Steven Bartlett, Diary of a CEO.
Alex Hormozi, acquisition.com.
Do you see where I am going?
So Play Ready Golf,
turning limited practice time into lower
scores.
App coming spring '26. Okay,
your app can be the app,
but we need someone to be the
personal brand, the founder of the app.
So again, Daniel Priestley, Score App.
That's what this needs to be.
Free 50 mind practice plan tracker.
Okay,
let's have a look at some of your
performance.
Only have 15 minutes at the driving range?
In the first five minutes,
I alternated targets
and shot shapes with a six
iron. The drill that I like the most,
it's a simple drill.
It's actually on-
Going to play the game of first three
seconds do I carry on?
Only have 15 minutes at the driving range?
In the first five minutes-
Music's a bit loud for my liking
... The drill that I like the most,
it's a simple drill.
It's a-
Don't care. Sorry.
Hashtags don't do anything, by the way.
They don't do anything.
So we can think about block practice
and random practice like this.
Keep in mind, these videos
are going to go to cold audiences.
So 100 random people,
do people vibe with it?
When I see you with a Shure SM7B in front
of you and a laptop behind you, I don't
think golf.
A lot of golf goals come off as
motivational posters.
If I was to put-
I feel like I'm just walking into a
conversation without a hook.
Being from Ohio,
the annual Christmas trip is a-
Don't care.
That's the difference now that we're get-
So I'm going to walk you through the
habits that can help you get better at
golf.
So I'm going to walk you through the
habits that are going to help you.
That part, just get rid of.
Get better at golf. Here's three ways.
Get so good at golf
that your friends start hating you
and stop inviting you to the
driving range. This is how.
We need to be so careful with the
first thing that we say. And also,
what I would love you to do,
say you've got this
hook here.
So I'm going to walk you through the
habits that can help you get better at
golf.
I want you to write down 10, 15 hooks,
whatever it is.
Go to a golfing environment
and film them there.
Walk into shot, golf club,
over the shoulder.
I'm going to give you four simple hooks
and then pay them off here.
Because one of the reasons I built a gym
isn't just the training.
The reason I built a gym
is so it can be in the background of the
first things that
I say in content. Now,
what you may notice in my fitness content
is there is always
colored bumper discs in the background
behind me.
Reason being, so that
when people start watching my content,
they know what's going
on. They go, "Oh,
probably a fitness reel." Why?
Because I'm using the gym.
Here are three ways you can get the most
out of playing golf on a simulator.
How many play golf on a simulator?
So just three simple tools
that ensure that you can transfer your-
This music's so loud. Keep in mind,
if you do this music a little bit too
quiet,
fine. A little bit too loud, hate you.
All right. It's freezing,
hence why I forgot to film an intro.
That's not a hook, mate.
So the whole deal with the Play Ready Golf
app is we build practice plans-
Okay, what I would love,
if you're a golf expert, start making
me fucking better at golf using this page.
I want you to help me so much
that it feels illegal that it's free.
I want you to come on this and I want...
What's your name, by the way, bro?
What is your name? Let's see
if I can find out. Play Ready Golf.
Play Ready Golf.
Josh Leder. Is that you, Josh? Josh,
I want you to become a fucking
legend online in the golf world.
Then I want you to have lead magnets to
help me
get golf at fucking phenomenal rates.
Then, once I'm on your lead magnet,
I want you to email me and go,
"I help people
get better at golf for a living.
So much so, I even created an app.
And the app makes it so easy,
you won't even need to pay for a golf
lesson again."
This belongs further down the funnel.
I have four S's.
My new iteration of Business Mentorship
3.0 that's going to come out next year is
going to surround the four S's. Social,
squeeze,
sell, scale. Now, your sell is here.
This is where I want to know about the
app. I don't care about the app
and socials.
I don't care about the app and squeeze.
I want to know about the app
when it comes to sell.
Can you do that for me, please, Josh?
And also, you need to get busy, brother.
Busy. Ryan, 858 posts,
which actually isn't that many
because he's predominantly on Twitter.
46,000 followers. He's a weapon.
You need to get busy, and also,
you need to be watching people like Ryan
like a
fucking hawk because let's say he's making
a million dollars a year.
Do you see him talking about his product
here? Not really.
I just see him turning up every fucking
day to help people get better at golf for
free. Success leaves clues, brother.
Good luck. Okay.
Total BJJ Nottingham. Once got kicked out
of, what was it? It wasn't Hooters, it
was another place.
Yeah, I fell asleep on a sofa. I
was drunk, and everyone bundled me
when I was
drunk, and it gave me a panic attack.
Imagine waking up from passing out,
not knowing where you are.
There's eight people on you.
So I grabbed the nearest guy to me,
whose name was
Redshaw, and I put him through a table.
It's interesting, like that.
Okay, Total BJJ Nottingham. Okay,
the branding is okay, because it could
be the brand of the gym,
Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu School
and Grappling Club.
I like the name, actually, Total BJJ.
I like it.
Okay,
let's have a look at some of the content.
Let's have a look at your link tree quick.
Class timetable, free trial. Here we go.
Join, website, Instagram. Okay.
What I would say here is,
maybe let's not have the
bottom four options. Okay,
so we had the four S's before: social,
squeeze,
sell, scale. So what we've had here is,
we've gone from social, those top
two help them go down to squeeze and sell.
These four keep them social.
So in essence, imagine I'm in
Nottingham in Hooters,
and I'm chatting to the barmaid, and
then she's getting to the end of her
shift, and I say,
"Shall we get out of here?"
And she says, "Yeah."
And then we walk out to the car park,
do a U-turn, and come
back into Hooters to have a drink.
You're like,
you've not really gone anywhere.
You know what I mean?
So I would get rid of those four,
because ultimately, if
someone's ready to have a look at your
offer and what you do, you don't want them
going somewhere like YouTube, because
if they click on YouTube,
they're going to go
to YouTube. They're going to go, "Oh,
this is kind of cool."
And then I'm going to
click on this, and I'm going to go, "Oh,
this is kind of cool." Then I'm going to
scroll down, I'm going to scroll down,
I'm going to scroll down,
and then I'm going
to end up going, "Oh,
Taki Moore has released something,"
and then I'm watching
Taki Moore's content, and I'm thinking,
"Oh, he's got a black belt, sister bear.
I'll race you to get a black belt,
brother." So yeah,
pretty much what I'm saying
is we don't want to send people away.
Really, what we want them to do
is inquire.
"Start your Jiu-Jitsu journey today.
Train with your..." Okay,
what I would say is maybe get rid of this
and just have
"Book my free class." Book my free class,
and you should say, "Come on in.
Come join us in the next few days.
Do a class next week." Because that's
really
what you want. And with Jiu-Jitsu,
once you get them in through the door,
that's
it. I'm sure this website is very good,
by the way.
You've got a lot of stuff here.
I'm very happy with this.
I like that you're in a lot of the
pictures as well.
And when they book a free class, which
is quite cool here, I've always imagined
it'd be quite cool where they could tick a
box, and it says, "Would you like a free
white belt with your trial class?" So
that when they come,
a white belt might cost
you £20,
but I've always thought about the
implication of giving
someone a white belt in this packet,
going, "There's no pressure on you coming
back, but because you came today
and you did a class,
you're now a white belt.
Here it is." Then they go home, and
if they're oohing
and aahing about joining,
they've just got this white belt sat on
their side.
First of all,
they're not going to go to another gym.
They're going to be like,
"I'm Team BJJ Nottingham for life." Then
they're going to
be like, "Oh,
this white belt either stays an ornament
or I fucking wear it
and become a blue belt." So there's one
for free, mate. There's one for free.
That's where I'd go with that. Also, here,
you say website, free
class. This is the same fucking thing,
brother.
So let's go book a free class
and then timetable.
That's all we need here, I think.
Let's have a look at some of these reels.
Okay, pretty decent views, actually.
Let's have a look.
Have you not heard of the scorpion lock?
Most people haven't.
Music's a bit loud, mate.
Music's a bit loud. Again,
I want to be able to hear.
If I feel overwhelmed and my senses
are overwhelmed, I'm gone,
and I don't know if
that's my neurodivergence
or that's just the way the game is played.
Here's the fastest way to tap somebody
from mount.
It's just like the music again.
Grab the collar on one side,
put your fingers in on the other side,
then just put
this-
Question, have you ever,
whilst teaching a class, asked
someone to please turn the music down so
your fucking students can hear
you as you're instructing?
If the answer has ever been yes, turn
the music down, brother.
Because that's what it is.
It's like you teaching a seminar with
fucking Fatman Scoop on
volume 120 in the back.
Second hand underneath the first hand,
lean your weight forwards.
Good technique.
If your partner's curled up here
and you can't get that second hook,
you put your
chin on their shoulder,
you're going to push your hips forwards as
you lean back,
and then you can stamp your-
I like this.
The having techniques here filmed is very
good.
Her head after this.
Three days, six days, three weeks.
Can you do me a favor?
Five weeks, five weeks. Try
and improve your frequency
is what I would do. This is good. This
is very good.
Until I win. Today's coach
is GI European champion, Irene Brooks.
At just 19 years old,
Irene has won GI Euro-
This is quite cool. I like this.
Get this guy in more to do more.
Also, Jiu-Jitsu niche.
I really want to do this with New Tonic
when it hits
Australia. Fighting strangers to see
if MMA works.
Fighting strangers to see
if Jiu-Jitsu works, 4.7 million views.
if Jiu-Jitsu works. So what this is,
is a bucket.
What's funny is,
I copied a fitness YouTube title the other
day, and I was like,
"Oh my God, you copied the guy's title."
Shut up. Now, fighting strangers to see
if MMA works, fighting strangers to see if
Jiu-Jitsu works. This works.
This video was the outlier.
Five million fucking views, brother.
Then other people have been using it,
and do you know what?
That's great,
because this wouldn't be getting
that many views unless
people are enjoying it.
Fighting strangers to see
if Jiu-Jitsu works, 800K.
This is good for the platform. This
is good for Jiu-Jitsu.
And I'm just going to show you this video
because it's one of my favorite fucking
videos in the world. Sorry.
You're wasting precious time.
It's my work account.
Hey, well...
Charles.
Hello, mate. I've got to keep filming.
There's some people.
Are they coming up on us?
Oh, yeah,
there's one trying to flank us on the far
right.
You put holes in my house.
All right.
Delete video from your phone.
Charles, Charles. Charles.
I thought you both made a movie or
something. Oi, come on.
Yeah, dude, you just... Yeah, let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Oh,
that fucking prick getting in his face.
I didn't know this guy's a big YouTuber.
Mathematical science, complex traps.
Oh, this is my kind of guy. Okay, sorry.
And this is why you don't send people to
YouTube.
This is exactly my point.
You see how I literally just proved my own
point
then?
If you send people to other social media
platforms to watch your stuff, yeah,
it could potentially work,
or the ADHD fuckheads could end up getting
distracted, and before they know it,
they've just found their new hero called
Charles,
who just fucking bangs out people who
think they're hard, which sounds
like my cup of tea.
I haven't been this excited since I
was one for you guys.
For any of you just relaxing on your sofa,
it's raining outside, you've got pit
patters of the rain on the window,
put on Dash cams Australia.
It's not even just to see car crashes.
It's the way that Aussies react.
It's like, "Fucking hell!"
Fucking idiot. Who the fuck? You reap...
What the fuck?
What the fuck? Another one.
What the-
That better be a cop car, surely.
Oh, anyway, see, this
is why you don't get into this. Fuck.
What are we doing?
I'm supposed to be reviewing content.
Right, I drove my car too hard yesterday.
I got an engine light
and a loss of pressure in one tire.
So I'm off to the tire man. You,
email address in the bottom,
put your fucking
socials in there so I can critique them.
And any of you that
are on the fence about it, this
is my advice.
Stop being a pussy, all right?
Because I could give you one bit of advice
that
changes your life. And one day,
you'll see me out and about,
and you'll say, "Oi,
that YouTube video you put out changed my
fucking life." I'll go, "Well, buy us a
beer then, you stingy prick." And
if you've already done that
and I've got your
details, then watch this video here,
because it's a video on something where I
speak about something
that could help you with something.
Bye-bye.